<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on QSCI 381 Labs</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on QSCI 381 Labs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Lab 03</title>
      <link>/2020/07/09/lab-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/07/09/lab-03/</guid>
      <description>Lab 03 Skills Slides  Lab 03 Report Template  Lab 03 Data  Homework For each question: show all mathematical work and include all code, plus output from R or graphs. Make sure to answer all sub-questions.
Problem 1 First, load and clean the data using the following code, being sure to insert the appropriate file path instead of PATH_TO_DATA.
# load package of helpful datasets and functions library(tidyverse) library(lubridate) # load data daily_rain &amp;lt;- readr::read_csv(&amp;quot;PATH_TO_DATA/seattleWeather_1948-2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lab 02</title>
      <link>/2020/07/02/lab-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/07/02/lab-02/</guid>
      <description>Lab 02 Skills Slides  Lab 02 Report Template  Homework For each question: show all mathematical work and include all code, plus output from R or graphs. Make sure to answer all sub-questions.
First, load and clean the data using the following code:
# load package of helpful datasets and functions library(tidyverse) # load data tuition_cost &amp;lt;- readr::read_csv(paste0( &amp;#39;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;rfordatascience/tidytuesday/master/&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;data/2020/2020-03-10/tuition_cost.csv&amp;#39;)) # remove other tuition_cost &amp;lt;- tuition_cost %&amp;gt;% filter(type !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lab 01</title>
      <link>/2020/06/24/lab-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/06/24/lab-01/</guid>
      <description>R Basics Slides  Lab 01 Skills Slides  Lab 01 Report Template  Practice and extension The ChickWeight dataset provides data on a sample of fifty chicks, each fed one of four different diets. For each chick, the data frame includes weight measurements at birth and every other day thereafter. First, load the data. You can use the commands:
# load ChickWeight dataset data(&amp;quot;ChickWeight&amp;quot;) Print out the weights of the chicks on day 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lab 00</title>
      <link>/2020/06/22/overview-of-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/06/22/overview-of-r/</guid>
      <description> Before your first lab section, you should work through the slides below to install R and check that all the software works on your computer.
Slides  Lab 00 Report Template If, when you download the template, you don’t see the header, you can copy and paste the header below:
--- title: &amp;quot;Lab 00 Report&amp;quot; author: &amp;quot;YOUR NAME HERE&amp;quot; date: &amp;quot;DATE HERE&amp;quot; output: html_document ---  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>